Just wondering. did we make this
more complicated than it had to be?
We could've easily killed them
then 'n' there.
Damn. how dense can you be?
Fighting them would've woken up the
boss. and our big payday would be gone.
That piece of crap E-Rank's
as weak as he is mopey.
Be a miracle for him and a D-Rank
without raid experience to beat that spider.
Once it eats 'em. it'll pass right back out.
and we can sneak in and claim our crystals.
I could break through
the cave-in with my magic.
Any explosion will wake the spider.
There were side tunnels
near the ceiling.
We'll drop in from there.
And the dots all connect.
Man. awesome idea.
But what if the spider's awake?
We'll chalk it up to bad luck
and take the damn thing out.
Either way. we're gonna come
out of this better than we went in.
Jinho's sword and shield alone
must be worth a few hundred million.
If we can't nab all the mana crystals.
his gear will have to do.
So let's figure out
whose trust fund kid he is.
Would look bad if I didn't show
at the funeral.
And you know without a doubt
those two were torn limb from limb
after our "noisy demolition".
A grumpy monster spider
can't be a good time.
Kyuhwan. Think you could take
that nasty bastard down yourself?
Yeah. right. maybe in
my wildest dreams.
I feel the same.
It's a beast of a magic beast.
So. yeah.
They're as good as dead.
That's the one part of my plan
that's an absolute guarantee.
Get serious! You'd have to be at least
a B-Rank to kill that on your own!
Or an upper C-Rank. which I'll
remind you is two ranks above you!
The odds are like zero. bro.
Let's focus our energy
on escaping instead!
Jinho has a point.
Even though I reawakened
and leveled up a few times.
I'm still pretty weak.
The blue venom-fanged kasaka I fought in
the instance dungeon was probably D-Rank.
Bet that golem was as well.
if not lower.
This thing's easily uglier
than both of them.
and safe to assume
it's stronger. too.
And yet somehow.
the thought of fighting it
doesn't intimidate me.
I can stand my ground
against a C-Rank boss.
I'm strong enough for that.
I'm level eighteen now.
Taking on this thing.
Is worth a shot!
They call us hunters for a reason.
And it's about time
the real hunt begins!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Long day. sir?
Seems these meetings
are beginning to wear on me.
They are on an endless loop.
The government. media. and
energy developers all wanna talk.
It's ironic. because I didn't
used to be much of a talker.
Thankfully. your schedule
is clear for the time being.
As such. would it be all right
if I asked for some instruction?
Could be a good change of pace.
Less talking. too.
They say old soldiers
are doomed to fade away.
but I can hardly turn down a
youngster asking for a bit of guidance.
That's one tough shell.
And it hits hard.
A single strike could kill me.
The way he's moving.
he can't possibly be E-Rank!
So what is he?
Huh? Did he fake his ranking?
It's not unheard of.
Some hunters have
exceptional magic control
and make it so they're ranked
lower when they register.
which earns them
the name "false rankers!"
Most turn out to be lunatics.
The kind of psychopaths
who kill for fun!
What am I even doing in this place?
Dad. I'm so sorry.
Damn! I still haven't done
any actual damage!
And with high fatigue. I'm
about to get real slow real fast.
I've gotta kill it
before that happens!
Paralysis and drain.
The dagger's debuffs
are my key to victory!
I just need a weak spot to aim for.
Gotcha!
Acid? Well. aren't you
full of nasty surprises!
This freak has rock-solid armor.
and spit that burns to the bone?
And the longer we fight.
the worse off I'll be.
I have to get up close.
regardless of the risk.
A new skill. Dash.
Perfect. let's take it for a spin!
If one hit won't cut it.
I'll just keep slicing away!
Whoa. he's fast!
But does he have
the stamina to hang in there?
What's his strategy?
Faster.
Go even faster!
Almost there!
Huh?
Oh. no! Jinwoo!
You can't die like this!
Man. am I glad I sat on those
daily quest rewards until now.
That could've ended
very differently otherwise.
I don't believe it.
He totally thrashed
that thing by himself!
Then it's true.
This guy is a false ranker!
Hmm. Wonder how much
this'll go for.
Hey. um. B-Boss?
If you'd like. I can hold all of
the essence stones you get.
I'd also be more than happy
to take care of your gear.
Thirsty. boss?
Please. help yourself.
I insist.
Uh. sure.
Why's he calling me that?
Sit back and rest up. boss!
I'll excavate the mana crystals
while you recharge!
What has gotten into him?
No. They're alive?
Are you all right?
I am. Thank you
for the lesson. sir.
I should thank you since this
was a good change of pace.
So thanks. Jinchul.
Remarkable. You don't seem
to have lost a step.
No. I have compared to
when I was on active duty.
What's really remarkable is how
much your defense has improved.
It shows you've been practicing.
Though I know my rank is set in
stone. there's nothing preventing me
from honing my body and technique.
Mm. It's important for hunters
to work on their minds and bodies
and not solely rely on their gifts.
Especially. since they're caught
in dire situations quite frequently.
It's in those same situations. that human
nature rears its ugly head to truly test you.
So you did squash the spider.
Guess it was just an overgrown
bug and not an overpowered monster.
I'm sure that dude's gear made
beating a C-Rank boss a cinch.
He's a D-Rank. though. Thing must've
been weak as hell for him to kill it.
So what's the call?
Just say the word.
I would think it's obvious.
Jinho Yoo!
Those fancy toys of yours got
me curious. so I did a little digging.
Your old man's the head of
Yoojin Construction. Myunghan Yoo.
Isn't that right?
Huh? Well. and so what if it is?
It's earned you a chance.
Kill Jinwoo and you'll live.
Surely the pieces have clicked.
We round out our numbers
with dumb chumps.
They all die. and we keep
their share of the loot.
And now. you're gonna be
our accomplice. Jinho Yoo.
That's the only way
you're leaving alive.
You're kidding.
Trust fund baby's first boss fight
was cake thanks to his special gear.
Could be a real pain to deal with.
Save yourself and kill him.
Or you can both die.
Come on. Not like it's a hard choice.
What happens in a dungeon
stays in a dungeon.
Don't tell me a D-Rank
is afraid of an E-Rank loser.
Huh?
Wow.
You're actually siding
with the deadweight?
So are we cooking
the golden goose. too. or what?
We'll take out the weak one first.
Say. fellas.
Ever killed a human before?
In cold blood?
Huh?
Wh... Urgent quest?
What the hell is this?
I would pay attention if I were you!
Boss!
Hey. Heejin!
It's been a while.
How're things down at
the White Tiger Guild lately?
It's business as usual.
Nothing really to report.
Any big news
out of the Hunter's Guild?
Nah. it's been
fairly normal for us too.
Wait a second.
How'd that training go?
Miss Cha led you through
an A-Rank dungeon. right?
That's not normal.
It was certainly something.
A fast something.
Our entire squad was struggling
against an A-Rank beast.
Then Miss Cha slayed it in a flash.
Made it look like it was
no big deal. either.
She took as all by surprise.
but Kihoon was just
completely bowled over.
He wants to be a strike team
captain. so it opened his eyes.
Yeah. he is pretty straight-laced.
What about that Chul Kim guy
from your guild?
Heard he also wants to be
a captain. Can he hack it?
He's not a bad guy
and he has potential. but...
But that one little word
tells us everything.
Guildmates aside.
think of how fortunate we are.
The guilds we joined
are the best of the best.
We're in the big leagues. ladies.
-That's very true.
-Mm-hmm.
I'd hate to freelance. especially with the
unsavory rumors I've heard floating around.
Rumors like what?
Like. you know.
Strike teams with suspiciously
high fatality rates.
Get a grip. kid.
Your friend is dead.
You murderers!
How could I have forgotten?
It's survival of the fittest
in this world.
This world filled with violence.
deception. and betrayal.
How could I?
How? How? How?
How? How? How? How?
That's right. I got numb to it.
Careless. overconfident. delusional.
And now. the system expects
me to murder my enemies.
Does it need to keep me alive
for some reason?
This isn't coincidence or charity.
The system wants me to live.
Huh?
It wants me strong.
Gosh. you sure know
how to take a hit. don't you?
"A hit?"
The dude took a deathblow.
I think I get it now.
If the system is bent on using me.
I'm just gonna have
to use the system.
Kyuhwan. you idiot.
You shouldn't have held back.
Thanks for the reminder.
The weak always lose. no matter what.
That's the way it is.
Somebody get this guy a medal.
The Weakest Hunter
of All Mankind understands!
I do. Your crew must understand
how it works. too. if you're saying that.
Hang on.
What crap are you talking?
You hunt and hunt.
So now I want to know if the
hunters are ready to be preyed upon.
Hey. boss. I'mma handle this one.
Okay. listen up. pal.
You need a reality check.
Are we "ready to be preyed upon"?
And just what can a jumped-up
little E-Rank like you even do?
I mean. you're the
Weakest Hunter of--
That's one down.
J-Juntae!
What the hell. man?
When did he draw that dagger?
Where was he even hiding it?
Arrogance aside. Juntae
was stronger than him!
How could an E-Rank kill a D-Rank?
I just killed somebody.
A person.
Even if I say
the system made me do it.
I still ended a man's life.
But it's either their lives or mine.
So I can't back down now.
Because it's only the strong
who survive!
Go to hell!
What kind of E-Rank moves like that?
Son of a bitch!
-Kyuhwan!
-Oh. um. right!
Die!
He's so strong.
And he seems even more powerful
than when he fought the dungeon boss.
You killed all five of my men
within seconds.
Bet you also took out
the spider. huh?
You kept your true strength
hidden from us!
Though I'm C-Rank like they were.
my Reinforcement sets me apart!
He's a monster in his own right. but
after fighting a boss and five hunters.
he has to be tired.
His speed and his dagger's special
abilities are what give him an edge.
But my Reinforcement skill
makes my body as strong as steel!
His attacks won't affect me!
Mister Hwang. you're impressive.
But I'm afraid I've got some
bad news for you.
You see. I've been leveling up
this whole time.
Wha-What just happened?
I think he smashed me
into the ground with one hand.
He lied. 'cause no way in hell
is he E-Rank!
Wait! Even a monster like you has to
have a heart. so show mercy and spare me!
You can take every mana crystal and
essence stone this dungeon has to offer!
In fact. I'll pay you on top of that!
Name any price you want to spare my life. and
I swear I'll double it no matter what it is!
-Two times whatever you want!
-Three times.
You tried to kill me
three times. didn't you?
And now you want mercy?
Yes! But for yourself!
You'll never get away with it
if you kill me here!
"What happens in
a dungeon stays in a dungeon."
Your words. not mine.
Bastard! If you had any idea
who my younger broth--
With the boss dead.
the gate's closing.
We have to go.
Mm?!
So all four C-Rank hunters
plus two D-Ranks died in action.
and the only survivors were a D-Rank
on his first raid and some rando E-Rank?
I know it sounds crazy. but it's true.
-I believe you!
-Oh! Do you?
Your blade. it's the Maya Company's Kalion
Longsword! It only just hit the shelves!
Yeah. that's quite an eye you have.
Rewards for slaughtering people.
The Murderous Intent skill?
Cuts enemy abilities
by 50% for a minute.
Yeah. of course. you'd live if you
had so much awesome equipment!
You must've been the hero of
this tragic tale. while this E-Rank hid
and let you handle everything
by yourself. Am I right?
Well. gentlemen. I appreciate
your cooperation after going
through such a disaster.
You are free to leave now.
E-Excuse me.
That was some
excellent work today. boss!
I really mean it!
Thanks.
Is there anything wrong?
No.
I was just thinking.
I'm glad I gave her that umbrella.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm